moschino.it 2017-06-18

# 

Welcome to **www.moschino.com**. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy applies when you visit and surf the US section of www.moschino.com (the “www.moschino.com US Site”) regardless of whether you purchase products, when you register with the www.moschino.com US Site, and when you use our services. If you have not already done so, please also read the General Terms and Conditions of Use of www.moschino.com, which contain important information on the security systems used by the www.moschino.com US Site. By using the www.moschino.com US Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use the www.moschino.com US Site.

The www.moschino.com Site is operated under license by **YNAP Corporation** (“YNAP”), a Delaware corporation having an address at 100 Fifth Avenue – 12th floor, New York, NY 10011, United States of America. YNAP is a subsidiary of **YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP S.p.A.** . (“YNAP S.p.A.”, together with YNAP collectively referred to herein as “ YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP” “we,” “us,” “our”), an Italian company having its registered address at via Morimondo, 17 – Milano 20143, Italy. YNAP and controls the personal data of users and customers of the www.moschino.com US Site together with **Moschino S.p.A.** , having address at Via San Gregorio 28, 20124, Italy, VAT, 02705970404 (Moschino). The users of the www.moschino.com US Site are referred to herein as “user,” “you,” “your.”

## 1\. OUR POLICY

YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino respect our users’ right to be informed about the collection and processing of their personal information. We will collect and process your information only in the manner and for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Further, we will use anonymous aggregate information whenever possible.

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with important information regarding our privacy practices. Should you have any questions regarding our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact our [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) by selecting “Privacy” from the drop-down menu, or sending a request to YNAP, YNAP S.p.A., or Moschino at the registered office indicated above.

## 2\. WHAT TYPE OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU AND HOW WE COLLECT IT

The information we collect from you when you use www.moschino.com US Site may be (i) personal information, which is information that personally identifies you, or (ii) aggregate information, which does not personally identify a user, but rather pertains to your use of the web site and your account activity (for example, number and times of log-ins, most frequently visited pages, IP addresses, etc.).  
The types of information we collect include the following:  

a. **Information you provide us.** When you enter information on www.moschino.com US Site by registering for My Account, subscribing to our newsletter, making a purchase or contacting [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare), for example, you give us access to certain personal information, which may include your name, email address, address, credit card information, and phone number.

b. **Information we collect automatically**. We automatically collect some information from the devices you use to access www.moschino.com US Site and to perform activities in the My Account section of the www.moschino.com US Site, such as device type, location information, IP address, webpage traffic, and access time. Automatic means of data collection include the use of cookies.

### Cookies

www.moschino.com US Site uses various types of cookies and similar technologies. A cookie is a small file that is sent to the browser and saved on your device when you visit a website like www.moschino.com US Site. While cookies do not contain intelligible information, they allow us to link a user to the personal information provided by such user through www.moschino.com US Site. www.moschino.com US Site uses analytical cookies, installed by both YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino, primarily to personalize your navigation experience by remembering your preferences with respect to services provided and products purchased through www.moschino.com US Site (for example, the IP address, the language and currency you set). We disseminate cookies in connection with functions such as browsing the catalogue, purchasing products on-line and supplying "My Account" services. YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino treat the results of these analyses anonymously. www.moschino.com US Site also uses third party marketing and profiling cookies, which are aimed at creating user-related profiles in order to send commercial messages that meet the preferences shown during web site visits or to provide you with our commercial offers on affiliated websites (retargeting). YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino do not have control over the information provided through third party cookies and we do not have access to this data. This information is entirely controlled by third parties as described in their respective privacy policies. As you may know, each Internet browser allows the deletion of cookies after each session and your Internet browser contains instructions on how to do so. Please access the instructions on your Internet browser if you wish to delete cookies.

Your acceptance of our automatic collection of information and the use of cookies is necessary to take advantage of many features and services offered by the www.moschino.com US Site, including the purchase of products. If you set your browser to block or delete cookies, we cannot guarantee that you will have access to all the features and services offered by the www.moschino.com US Site (for example, your computer may not be able to display the image of the product you are in the process of purchasing).

### How we respond to Do Not Track Signals

You can easily activate the “Do Not Track Signal” by accessing the DNT instructions section of your browser through the following links:

IE: <https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17288/windows-internet-explorer-11-use-do-not-track>  
Safari:<https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21416?locale=en_US>  
Chrome:[https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/2790761?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/2790761?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en)  
Firefox: [ https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/how-do-i-turn-do-not-track-feature](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/how-do-i-turn-do-not-track-feature)

Third parties that provide content or services through the www.moschino.com US Site, such as social media features, may obtain aggregate information about your browsing activities, but such information does not include personally identifiable information. However, certain processing activities that combine aggregate information with other information in possession of such third parties could result in the identification of users.

c. **Information we receive from other sources.** YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino may collect information from third parties to whom you have provided your information and given consent to such third parties’ sale, rental or transfer of such information (for example, through social media sites); we may also integrate the information we collect with publicly available information.

## 3\. WHO PROCESSES YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND TO WHOM IT IS DISCLOSED

We may share your information with companies affiliated with YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and/or Moschino , their licensees and joint venture partners, affiliated companies may be located outside of the United States. In the event there is a change in the corporate structure of YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP or Moschino including, without limitation, by merger, consolidation, sale, liquidation, or transfer of substantial assets, YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP or Moschino , as applicable, may, in their sole discretion, transfer, sell or assign personal data collected on and through the www.moschino.com US Site, including, without limitation, personally identifiable information and aggregate information concerning users and customers, to one or more affiliated or unaffiliated third parties through such transaction.

YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino have appointed certain entities that will process personal information of users and customers of the www.moschino.com US Site for purposes such as providing IT services, logistics services, product shipping, payment services, customer support or marketing services. These data processors may only use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and disclosure will not exceed the purpose for which your information was collected and processed.

Third parties who provide these services have been appropriately selected and have only been authorized to use the information disclosed to them to perform their duties and for no other purpose. The above-mentioned data processors have been chosen by YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino because of their experience in processing personal data, their sufficient guarantees with respect to compliance with applicable laws and regulations, including the Italian Data Protection Code (Legislative Decree no. 196 of 30 June 2003) as well as the technical security measures adopted by them in connection with the processing of personal data. In processing personal information of the users of the www.moschino.com US Site, our processors will act only in accordance with instructions provided by YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino . We regularly verify that our processors comply with our instructions and that they provide sufficient guarantees with respect to their compliance with applicable laws and regulations. Companies involved in the processing of personal information of users and customers of the www.moschino.com US Site include, without limitation:

  * United Parcel Service S.p.A. and its affiliates ("UPS"): we provide UPS with customers’ addresses and other personal information by electronic means for the purpose of shipping, delivering and returning products purchased on the www.moschino.com US Site;
  * BT Italia S.p.A., for purposes related to the maintenance of YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP servers;
  * Interconnexia Ltd.: we provide Interconnexia with customers’ contact details for purposes connected to providing call center and customer care services to www.moschino.com US Site's users;
  * Newtek Business Services Corp. (“Newtek”): we provide Newtek with customers’ credit card numbers and billing information, for purposes connected to providing electronic payment services, through credit/debit cards.

Please contact our Customer Service by selecting “Privacy” from the drop-down menu if you would like to receive a full list of our data processors.

In addition, your personal information may be disclosed to third parties in order to (1) comply with applicable laws, (2) respond to governmental and judiciary inquiries, (3) comply with valid legal processes, and (4) protect the rights and/or property of YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino (e.g. defense of legal claims or for fraud prevention purposes).

Your personal information will not be transferred to any countries outside the United States or Italy if such countries do not provide for an adequate level of privacy protection. Should such transfer be necessary in order to supply services to you or fulfill purchase orders, YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino will enter into agreements with third parties to ensure that they implement measures to safeguard users’ information, in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

## 4\. HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION AND FOR WHAT PURPOSES

Your personal information is collected and processed by YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino for purposes related to your use of the www.moschino.com US Site and the provision of services to you through the www.moschino.com US Site, including to enable you to engage in the purchase of products.

Specifically, your personal information may be used, among others, for the following purposes:

  * PURCHASING: When you complete checkout procedures to purchase products sold on the www.moschino.com US Site, we collect your personal information (for example, name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card numbers, and telephone number) for the purpose of selling the products ordered by you and managing your payment, including anti-fraud control when paying by credit/debit card;
  * CUSTOMER ASSISTANCE: When you request [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) assistance, we collect your personal information (for example, your first and last name, e-mail address and password) to provide you with [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) relevant to the www.moschino.com US Site and to the purchase of products on the www.moschino.com US Site;
  * SERVICE REGISTRATION: When you register with the www.moschino.com US Site, we collect your personal information (for example, your name, e-mail address) through the relevant registration form (My Account), in order to provide you with services in reserved access areas of the www.moschino.com US Site and to send you our Newsletter, when you have subscribed for it;
  * MARKETING: We use your email address, phone number and mailing address to send commercial communications through various channels, both electronic (e-mail, text messages) and traditional (snail mail, telephone);
  * PROFILING: We may use your information to send commercial offers that match your interests (for example, through the use of third party cookies), for profiling purposes and in order to improve your user experience.

YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino may have access to third parties’ personal information which is directly disclosed by their users to YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino , for instance when the user buys a product to be sent to a friend, when the user who pays for a product is different from the recipient of such product, or when a user wishes to recommend to a friend a service provided through the www.moschino.com US Site or a particular product posted on the www.moschino.com US Site. When disclosing information concerning a third party to YNAP, YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and/or Moschino , you guarantee that you have obtained the consent of such individuals in advance and have informed them about this Privacy Policy.

Your personal information is generally processed by electronic means, however, in certain circumstances, paper-based means may be used, for example, for processing related to fraud prevention purposes. Your personal information is stored in a way which allows YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino to identify you for the time necessary to carry out the purposes for which such information is collected and processed.

## 5\. WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU DO NOT DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

The personal information we request you to provide to YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino , including your e-mail address, your address, your credit/debit card number, and your telephone number, is necessary to process your purchase order for products on the www.moschino.com US Site, to supply other services provided on the www.moschino.com US Site, or to carry out our obligations arising out of applicable laws and regulations.  
Your refusal to provide certain information to YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino may prevent YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino from processing your purchase order or from providing other services through the www.moschino.com US Site, such as [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) s, sending our Newsletter, accessing the Wish List, recommending a product to a friend. .  
The disclosure of your information to YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino may be mandatory or optional. Disclosure is mandatory when needed to process purchase orders or provide requested services on the www.moschino.com US Site. We will inform you if the information we ask you to provide is necessary or optional by marking with an asterisk (*) the information that is required. Your failure to disclose optional information will not entail any disadvantage to you, except to the extent that we may not be able to offer you some of our optional, personalized features of the www.moschino.com US Site.

## 6\. WHERE IS YOUR INFORMATION STORED

Your information will be collected and stored on servers located in Italy. By providing us with your information you consent to its use and processing in the US and its transfer to Italy for the same purposes, regardless of the country from which you access the web site.

## 7\. CHILDREN’S RIGHTS

While www.moschino.com does not sell products or services for purchase by children, we may sell children’s products or services for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use the www.moschino.com US Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), www.moschino.com does not knowingly collect, solicit or use personal information of children under the age of 13 provided without parental consent, and www.moschino.com will delete any such information should we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has registered without verifiable parental consent. Therefore, if you are not 18 years or older, you are not authorized to use our US Site.

## 8\. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED FROM OR SHARED WITH SOCIAL MEDIA SITES

When accessing www.moschino.com US Site through a third party social media site and/or application, you consent to YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino’s access to some of your information from your social media account, such as your name, email address, profile picture, location, friend list, posts and likes. Furthermore, additional non-personally identifiable information may be transferred to us when interacting with a social media site, for example information regarding content viewed through the third party social media site.

Some of the services offered on the www.moschino.com US Site are integrated with social sharing features, through which you may share some of your activities on the web site or “like” certain products through your social media accounts. Depending on your settings on your social media accounts, these activities may show up on your profile and be visible to your friends/followers and/or the public. Please refer to the privacy policies of the relevant social media sites for information concerning their collection and processing of information.

## 9\. MOBILE/APP TERMS AND CONDITIONS

Please refer to the principles stated in this Privacy Policy when accessing the mobile version of www.moschino.com US Site or its mobile application. You will find this Privacy Policy directly on the mobile version of the site you are visiting. If you have any questions regarding these privacy practices and the related Privacy Policy, please contact our Customer Service by selecting “Privacy” from the drop-down menu, or by inserting “Privacy” as a subject.

## 10\. SECURITY MEASURES

We have adopted security measures to protect information data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access and against other unlawful forms of data processing, as provided in our Privacy Policy. We restrict access to information only to employees, contractors and agents that need to process information for the purposes set forth herein. Nevertheless, neither YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP nor Moschino can guarantee that the security measures adopted for the protection of the www.moschino.com US Site and the transmission of data and information through the www.moschino.com US Site will prevent or exclude any risk of unauthorized access to or loss of data; any transmission of information is at your own risk. It is advisable that your computer be equipped with software devices for the protection of network data transmission and receipt (such as, updated antivirus systems) and that your Internet service provider take appropriate measures for the security of network data transmission (such as, firewalls and anti-spam filtering).

When processing your credit card information in connection with the purchase of products on the www.moschino.com US Site, we comply with PCI DSS standards.

## 11\. OPT OUT

You may unsubscribe from any marketing communications by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” button included in all of our marketing communications or by contacting our [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) through the appropriate section on #US Site selecting “Privacy” as the topic on our contact form.

## 12\. YOUR RIGHT TO ACCESS PERSONAL DATA AND FURTHER RIGHTS

You are entitled to obtain, at any time, confirmation from YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino as to whether or not your information is being processed, and the communication of any such data in an intelligible form. Moreover, you are entitled to receive from YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino information on the source from which we received your personal information; the purposes and means of processing; information regarding the data controller and the data processors and the names and categories of third parties to whom your personal information may be disclosed or who may access your personal information. Please contact our [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) by selecting “Privacy” from the drop-down menu if you would like to receive a full list of our data processors.

You are entitled to request at any time that YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino update, rectify, integrate or delete your personal information, provided retention is not required by law. Please report any changes to your personal information, in order to ensure that it is always accurate and up-to-date, or exercise your other rights discussed above by contacting our [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare), by selecting “Privacy” from the drop-down menu. Some of your personal information may need to be retained by YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino as required by law or for recordkeeping purposes. Please note that by withdrawing consent to our use of some of your information you may no longer be able to access certain services offered on the www.moschino.com US Site.

## 13\. RIGHTS OF CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Pursuant to California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with the California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: www.ftc.gov.

If you are a resident of California, you may request that we not share your information with certain affiliates or third parties providers for marketing purposes, and/or you may inquire as to how we have shared your information with third parties providers for marketing purposes. In connection with such request, we will identify the types of information shared and provide you with the names and addresses of the third parties with whom the information was shared. Please contact our [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) through the appropriate form selecting “Privacy” as the topic on our contact form.

## 14\. LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

The www.moschino.com US Site may provide hyperlinks to third party websites (the “Third Party Websites”). Neither YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP nor Moschino operates, controls, endorses or guarantees any Third Party Websites. You agree that YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino are not responsible for any content, services and/or products provided by any Third Party Website, and that YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino are not responsible for any practice followed by such Third Party Website with respect to the collection and processing of personal information of their users. YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino provide hyperlinks to Third Party Websites only for the convenience of our users. By providing hyperlinks to Third Party Websites, YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino do not recommend that users access such Third Party Websites.

Our Privacy Policy and other policies on www.moschino.com US Site do not apply to any Third Party Website. When you access any Third Party Website through a hyperlink posted on the www.moschino.com US Site, please carefully read the Privacy Policy and other policies of such Third Party Website.

You agree that your use of any Third Party Website is at your sole risk and without warranties of any kind by YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP, YNAP, and/or Moschino expressed, implied or otherwise, including, but not limited to, warranties of title, fitness for a particular purpose, merchantability or non infringement and under no circumstances are YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP, YNAP, and/or Moschino liable for damages arising from any transaction between you and any third party website or for any information appearing on Third Party Websites.

## 15\. CONTACTS

If you wish to receive further information regarding our privacy practices, please contact our Customer Service by selecting “Privacy” from the drop-down menu or by sending a mail to the addresses provided above.

## 16\. ACCESSIBILITY ISSUES

Although we have done our best to make the www.moschino.com US Site fully accessible to all users, if you have any problems with or questions about accessibility, please do not hesitate to contact us.

## 17\. GOVERNING LAW

The processing of personal data by YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino will be conducted in compliance with applicable US laws, any claims or complaints must be filed in the United States in the State of New York. Since personal information of users and customers of the www.moschino.com US Site may be processed in Italy, Italian law, including the Italian Personal Data Protection Code (Legislative Decree no. 196 dated June 30, 2003), also applies to the processing of personal information carried out by YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino . The Italian Personal Data Protection Code guarantees that the processing of your personal data will be carried out in compliance with the fundamental rights and freedoms of individuals and their dignity, with particular reference to confidentiality, personal identity and the right to personal data protection.

## 18\. MODIFICATION AND UPDATING

YOOX NET-A-PORTER GROUP and Moschino may amend or update from time to time all or any part of this Privacy Policy, whether or not required by a change in the applicable laws and regulations. Our users will be notified of any amendment to or update of our Privacy Policy on our homepage. If you have provided your email address when registering the My Account service, subscribing to our Newsletter, making a purchase or contacting [Customer Service](https://www.moschino.com/customercare) , we will notify you via email if material changes are made to this Privacy Policy. All amendments and updates will become effective upon publication on this section of the www.moschino.com US Site. You should regularly access this section of the www.moschino.com US Site in order to review the most recent and updated version of our Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 2017.

Back to top
